don't say rule it all out
すべてを排除しろとは言わないでください
don't do anything
何もしないでください
don't go too far
あまり遠くに行かないでください
we're talking about a trend
私たちはトレンドについて話しています
What kind of food is the person who chooses
選ぶ人はどんな食べ物なのか
He's not weak
彼は弱くない
Of course, first of all, look at the international
もちろん、まずは国際情勢に目を向けてください。
what kind of information
どのような情報ですか
because he is so famous
彼はとても有名なので
so almost what disease
それで、ほとんど何の病気ですか
Take it with mediterranean diet
誰もが地中海食を持ち込む
let's discuss
話し合いましょう
when you were middle-aged
あなたが中年の頃
overeating or when old
過食または高齢の場合
long-term intake
長期摂取
If it is the form of the Mediterranean diet
それが地中海食の形なら
Less prone to frailty
虚弱になりにくい
Conversely, if it is a Western diet
逆に、西洋的な食生活であれば、
Just a lot of red meat burgers vegetarian
赤身肉のハンバーガーだけベジタリアン
It is easier to suffer from debilitation
衰弱しやすくなる
This is a study of Westerners
これは西洋人の研究です
But after all, there is no way we can combine the Mediterranean diet
しかし結局のところ、地中海食を組み合わせることはできません
apply to Taiwan
台湾に申請する
learn a little
少し学ぶ
but there is no way to completely
しかし完全に解決する方法はありません
it looks like this
このように見えます
people eat
人々は食べる
It's not about how much you eat
どれだけ食べるかが問題なのではない
Rather it is the emergence of a form
むしろそれは形の出現です
Suppose I eat a lot of red meat
赤身の肉をたくさん食べるとします
I have no room in my stomach for tofu
お腹に豆腐を入れるスペースがない
or fish and shrimp
または魚やエビ
So food is a way of appearance
つまり、食べ物は見た目の手段です
We made such a rule of thumb
私たちはそのような経験則を作りました
Then found a diet mentality
それからダイエットの考え方を見つけました
What about Kina?
キナはどうですか？
Eating adequate amounts of plant-based foods
適切な量​​の植物ベースの食品を食べる
Contains fruits and vegetables
果物と野菜が含まれています
lotus seed oil
蓮の実油
such food and drink
そんな食べ物や飲み物
ok so tea is a drink
はい、お茶は飲み物です
That will provide phytochemicals
それは植物化学物質を提供します
so apart from what we know
私たちが知っていることとは別に
fiber nutrients minerals
食物繊維、栄養素、ミネラル
There is also a so-called phytochemical
いわゆるフィトケミカルもあります
You can see these proteins
これらのタンパク質を見ることができます
is less saturated fat
飽和脂肪が少ない
We all know that saturated fat causes inflammation
飽和脂肪が炎症を引き起こすことは誰もが知っています
when the body is aging
体が老化すると
I just talked about the body having a low-grade inflammation
体に軽度の炎症があることについてお話しました
then this will affect
そうすればこれは影響します
Your body's protein synthesis
体のタンパク質合成
According to the information just now
今の情報によると
We organize it like this
このように整理します
just take a look
ちょっと見てください
For the prevention and treatment of senile dementia
老人性認知症の予防と治療に
Tips for this diet
このダイエットのヒント
Moet's disease is a variety of nutrients
モエ病はさまざまな栄養素
The condition of low intake
摂取量が少ない状態
but other than protein
でもプロテイン以外にも
other these
その他これら
we really don't know
私たちは本当に知りません
who is a key factor
誰が重要な要素なのか
interventional research
介入研究
You observed that first let
あなたは最初にそれを観察しました
Such a thing is given to the weak
そんなものは弱い者に与えられる
Let's see if he eats well
彼がよく食べるかどうか見てみましょう
Anyway, the only thing that can be proven
とにかく証明できるのはこれだけ
so what
だから何
From the information on the diet form just now,
先ほどのダイエットフォームの情報から、
we just wanted to say
私たちはただ言いたかっただけです
if we follow
私たちが従えば
This from the US-Japan Dietary Guidelines
これは日米食事ガイドラインより
This way of taking a balanced diet is recommended for the elderly
高齢者にはバランスの良い食事がおすすめ
What if he does this?
彼がこれをしたらどうなるでしょうか？
He will first ensure that the nutrients are up to standard
彼はまず栄養素が基準を満たしていることを確認します
Contains protein will hit the mark
プロテインが含まれているので的中します
Of course the low calorie one
もちろん低カロリーのもの
We're going to tweak the protein
プロテインを調整してみます
Improved overall nutritional status
全体的な栄養状態の改善
may be beneficial
有益かもしれない
whole body system
全身系
Maintenance of function and muscle mass
機能と筋肉量の維持
That's the premise of a hypothesis we made
それが私たちが立てた仮説の前提です
that is
あれは
There is an important element that is
重要な要素があります、それは
More than 1500 calories
1500カロリー以上
Protein is really okay
プロテインは本当に大丈夫
But what if it's under 1500 calories?
しかし、1500カロリー未満の場合はどうなるでしょうか？
still need to make some adjustments
まだ調整が必要です
This paper only mentions that
この論文ではそれについてのみ言及しています
If you are someone with different calories
カロリーが違う人なら
Oh 1300, 1400, 1600 to
ああ、1300、1400、1600へ
The amount of meals everyone eats is slightly different
食べる量は人それぞれ微妙に違う
The protein will go up slowly
プロテインはゆっくり上がっていきます
vegetable
野菜
fruit
フルーツ
besides
そのほか
our word in taiwan
台湾での私たちの言葉
what we suggest
私たちがどのように提案するか
The category is stable and has not increased
カテゴリは安定していて増加していません
But on protein and protein
しかし、プロテインとプロテインについては
There is a scaling like this
こんな感じのスケールがあります
Then like this grease also goes up
するとこんな感じでグリスも上がります
So this data is hard to remember
したがって、このデータは覚えにくいです
enter your own data in
独自のデータを入力してください
then find your combination
それからあなたの組み合わせを見つけてください
you just write it down
それを書き留めるだけです
keep for reference
参考のために保管してください
want to look like this
こんなふうになりたい
in the literature
文献の中で
If we look at the international literature
海外の文献を見てみると
Found this with Shi Zhixixi
Shi Zhixixi でこれを見つけました
There are quite a lot of related nutrients
関連する栄養素がたくさんあります
Contains vitamin B complex
ビタミンB群が含まれています
Vitamin C Vitamin E Vitamin D
ビタミンC ビタミンE ビタミンD
There are also various plant chemicals
植物化学物質もいろいろあります
The most notable research it shows is that
それが示す最も注目すべき研究は、
It is more certain that it is the intervention of vitamin B group
ビタミンB群の介入であることがより確実です
Vitamin B complex has several B
ビタミンB群にはいくつかのBが含まれています
Contains folic acid Grain number B2 Grain number B6
葉酸配合 粒番号B2 粒番号B6
All of these follow
これらすべてが続きます
the synthesis of our neurotransmitters
神経伝達物質の合成
They use MRI to measure the volume of the brain
彼らはMRIを使用して脳の体積を測定します
It was found that head and group B
先頭とグループBであることが判明
Can significantly slow down shrinkage
収縮を大幅に遅らせることができる
is now international
今では国際的です
The only study with good results
良い結果が得られた唯一の研究
But we believe this Shi Zhixihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihi
しかし、私たちはこれを信じます Shi Zhixihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihihi
Quality also sees group B when cutting in with nutrients
栄養素を取り入れた場合、品質はグループ B にも見られます
What about the Nutritional Health Survey?
栄養健康調査についてはどうですか?
It is also found that it is related to this system
このシステムと関係があることも判明
It's the people with low MMSE scores
MMSEスコアが低い人たちです
it's basically a lot of stuff
それは基本的にたくさんのことです
very low heat
非常に低い熱
protein fat with carbohydrates
炭水化物を含むタンパク質脂肪
B1 B2 B3 is nice
B1 B2 B3 いいですね
B6 B12 CDE
B6 B12 CDE
False Calcium Maxim Zero Iron
偽カルシウムマキシムゼロ鉄
Fatty Acid Regardless of Saturated Units
飽和単位を問わない脂肪酸
low in cholesterol and low in fiber
低コレステロール、低繊維
So here is a phenomenon that appears when people get old
人が年をとると現れる現象です
Didn't you usually have heart disease and high cholesterol in the past?
以前は心臓病や高コレステロールを患っていませんでしたか?
but by then
でもそれまでに
You have heart disease, high cholesterol
心臓病、高コレステロールを患っている
At that time, it was not high anymore. They all came down.
その時はもう水位は高くなくて、みんな降りてきました。
So this time is to eat more
ということで、今回はもっと食べてみようと思います
After seeing such a result
そんな結果を見てから
I think the diet of the last group of the elderly can be integrated
最後の高齢者グループの食生活を統合できると思います
Because the difference between weakening and restraining is not too big
弱体化と抑制の差が大きすぎないから
It is these proteins that must be taken care of
注意しなければならないのはこれらのタンパク質です
it's probably almost
おそらくほぼです
low calorie intake
低カロリー摂取
Many macro and trace elements have lower levels of pearls to contain those
多くのマクロおよび微量元素は、それらを含有するために真珠のレベルが低くなります。
something that shouldn't be high
就不該高的東西
like cholesterol and saturates
コレステロールや飽和物など
We both said we must
私たちは二人ともそうしなければならないと言った
something low
低要低的東西
Now instead of saying
今は言う代わりに
your cholesterol but don't limit it
あなたのコレステロールを制限しないでください
Don't limit the meat
肉を制限しないでください
Because now it's just a matter of eating too little
今はただ食べる量が少ないだけだから
Well, cognitive function is good
まあ、認知機能は良好です
what about the elderly
高齢者はどうですか
we just saw
私たちはちょうど見たところです
fresh fruits
新鮮な果物
Whago Whole Milk
ワゴー全乳
protein rich food
たんぱく質が豊富な食べ物
Like a man is fish Han seafood
男は魚のような漢海鮮
Women are eggs or soy products
女性は卵か大豆製品
and tea and coffee
そして紅茶とコーヒー
a form of sauce
ソースの一種
So our Taiwan
それで私たちの台湾
with the international
国際的なものと
is very consistent
非常に一貫しています
In the long run, it starts from middle age
長い目で見れば中年から始まる
Of course you want to prevent
もちろん防ぎたいのは
cardiovascular disease
循環器疾患
This kind of thing like three high
三高みたいなこういうこと
let this risk down
このリスクを軽減しましょう
short term
短期
You need to get enough nutrients
十分な栄養素を摂取する必要があります
group b is enough
グループBで十分
enough protein
十分なタンパク質
tea or enough
お茶でも十分
Inside the National Construction Agency's plan
建設庁計画の中身
we suggest
私たちは提案します
The key to housing for geriatric syndrome
老人症候群のための住まいの鍵
Diet content
食事内容
that is to say the first point
つまり最初のポイント
You must balance the six categories
6 つのカテゴリのバランスを取る必要があります
for those who eat less
食べる量が少ない人にとっては
The allocation of these six categories should be adjusted
これら 6 つのカテゴリの割り当てを調整する必要があります
we must emphasize
私たちは強調しなければなりません
what i just said
私が今言ったこと
Vegetables, Nuts, Seed Circles, Dairy
野菜、ナッツ、シードサークル、乳製品
and protein-rich foods
そしてたんぱく質が豊富な食べ物
with healthy tea
健康茶と一緒に
In terms of protein, what is better for the elderly?
タンパク質に関しては、高齢者にとって何が良いのでしょうか？
Fish and seafood, including excuses
魚介類（言い訳も含む）
Egg Bean Meat
卵豆肉
As for meat, less red meat
肉は赤身が少ない
but it means to say
しかしそれは言うことを意味します
People who eat less red meat
赤身の肉をあまり食べない人
Other people who eat a lot of meat are good
肉をたくさん食べる他の人は良いです
But let's analyze it carefully
しかし、それを注意深く分析しましょう
People with fewer lions and less sour meat
ライオンと酸っぱい肉が少ない人々
did he eat red meat
彼は赤身の肉を食べましたか
he still has
彼はまだ持っています
don't say exclude it all
全部除外とは言わないでください
don't do anything
何もしないでください
don't go too far
あまり遠くに行かないでください
we're talking about a trend
私たちはトレンドについて話しています
intervention target
介入目標
We are doing the same in the community now
私たちは今コミュニティでも同じことをしています
The first time we met an old man
初めて老人に会ったとき
We want to shun his personal heat
私たちは彼の個人的な熱を避けたいのです
Then we understand his six categories of allocation
次に、彼の 6 つの割り当てカテゴリーを理解します。
we are going to tell him
私たちは彼に言うつもりです
and then assign it
そしてそれを割り当てます
how to adjust his main meal
主食の調整方法
Distribution of the four food groups
4つの食品グループの分布
what is it like
それはどんな感じですか
What kind of staple food
主食は何ですか
Main course
主菜類
what kind of vegetables
どのような野菜ですか
what kind of fruit to match
どんなフルーツが合うのか
What about the allocation?
配分はどうなるのでしょうか？
we would recommend using some
いくつか使用することをお勧めします
three-dimensional space
三次元空間
plate you can easily understand
わかりやすいプレート
Then we ordinary people
それでは私たち一般人は
you can buy one
1つ購入できます
After I got to know it, it took me a while to do yours.
それを知ってから、あなたのことをするまでに時間がかかりました。
That amount is rooted in your mind
その金額はあなたの心に根付いています
Where do you go out in the future, let alone take it with you
将来どこに出かけるの、ましてや持って行きますか？
And that means creatively
それは創造的な意味で
There are some things you may not normally be used to
普段は慣れないこともありますが、
You need to have some imagination and creativity
想像力と創造力が必要です
mix it in
混ぜてください
Many of our friends are playing this activity all day long
私たちの友達の多くは一日中このアクティビティをプレイしています
how to play this match how to match
この試合のプレイ方法 試合方法
Then post it on Facebook.
次に、それを Facebook に投稿します。
Then pass it back and forth in LINE
あとはLINEでやりとりする
Very interesting
とても興味深い
This can be turned into an event
これはイベント化できる
For example, a situation in our family is
たとえば、私たちの家族の状況は次のとおりです。
my mother
私の母
My mother is a hundred years old now
私の母はもう百歳です
she is also very healthy
彼女もとても健康です
But she does eat less
しかし、彼女は食べる量が減りました
If there are vegetables left over from lunch or dinner
昼食や夕食で野菜が残っている場合
then we'll collect it
それから私たちがそれを集めます
For example, the next morning
例えば、翌朝、
i'll chop it up
私はそれを切り刻みます
then with an egg
それから卵で
turn into vegetable eggs
野菜の卵に変わる
then put it on the sandwich
それからサンドイッチに置きます
For example like this
たとえばこのように
then you just make sure it's veggies
それからそれが野菜であることを確認するだけです
will eat
食べる
This is an example
これは一例です
If it's fruit, it's me
それが果物なら、それは私です
My mother only has one appetite a day
私の母は一日に一度しか食欲がありません
fruit that can only be eaten once
一度しか食べられない果物
She can't eat in the afternoon and evening
彼女は午後と夕方には食事をすることができません
so i must help her with breakfast
だから私は彼女の朝食を手伝わなければなりません
prepare a bowl of fruit
フルーツのボウルを準備する
arrive
到着
if i go home at noon
正午に家に帰ったら
I'll pour her a glass
彼女にグラスを注ぎます
100 percent orange juice
100パーセントオレンジジュース
put on the table
テーブルの上に置く
She will see it at noon
彼女は正午にそれを見るでしょう
i'm busy
私は忙しいんだ
if i forget
忘れたら
i go home at night
夜には家に帰ります
Arrive home at half past five
5時半に家に到着
I'll start with a glass of 100 percent orange juice
まずは100パーセントのオレンジジュースを一杯
or grape juice
またはブドウジュース
put it over there
そこに置いてください
just ask her to drink first
彼女に最初に飲むように頼んでください
then wait until i make dinner
それから夕食を作るまで待ってください